♪♪
♪ I walk a lonely road ♪
♪ The only one that I have ever known ♪
♪ Don't know where it goes ♪
♪ But it's home to me and I walk alone ♪
♪ I walk this empty street ♪
♪ On the Boulevard of Broken Dreams ♪
♪ Where the city sleeps ♪
♪ And I'm the only one and I walk alone ♪
♪ I walk alone ♪
♪ I walk a ♪
♪ My shadow's the only one that walks beside me ♪
♪ My shallow heart's the only thing that's beating ♪
♪ Sometimes I wish someone out there will find me ♪
♪ 'Til then I walk alone ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, aaah-ah ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah ♪
♪ I'm walking down the line ♪
♪ That divides me somewhere in my mind ♪
♪ On the border line ♪
♪ Of the edge and where I walk alone ♪
♪ Read between the lines ♪
♪ Of what's f**ked up and everything's alright ♪
♪ Check my vital signs ♪
♪ To know I'm still alive and I walk alone ♪
♪ I walk alone ♪
♪ I walk a ♪
♪ My shadow's the only one that walks beside me ♪
♪ My shallow heart's the only thing that's beating ♪
♪ Sometimes I wish someone out there will find me ♪
♪ 'Til then I walk alone ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, aaah-ah ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah ♪
♪ I walk alone ♪
♪ I walk a ♪
♪♪
♪ I walk this empty street ♪
♪ On the Boulevard of Broken Dreams ♪
♪ Where the city sleeps ♪
♪ And I'm the only one and I walk a ♪
♪ My shadow's the only one that walks beside me ♪
♪ My shallow heart's the only thing that's beating ♪
♪ Sometimes I wish someone out there will find me ♪
♪ 'Til then I walk alone ♪
♪♪